





06.03.2001



Ho Chi Minh City

An enthusiastic marketer with strong passion for Brand, Data, and Communication, gaining lots of valuable experience to cultivate the professional mindset and form a good business acumen. I am dedicated to work with a curiosity and can-do attitude, hunger to learn and continuously utilize opportunities to develop myself to make a meaningful impact to business.

### WORKING EXPERIENCE

# **M N WORKFLOW SPACE** FLUM July 2024 - Present

## **Marketing Specialist**

- Content Development: Developing engaging and informative content aligned with branding & performance goals across communication channels (POSM, Social Media, Landing Page, Banner App,...); boosted page followers by 82% in 7 months
- Creative Development: Designing & adapting visuals or collaborating with designers to develop visually appealing and effective marketing assets, ensuring alignment with brand guideline and campaign objectives
- Digital Performance: Collaborating with digital to produce & implement adjustments to content & visuals for ads campaigns, ensuring optimal performance within budget; achieved 500K+ reach at a CPM of 5.000d for the early sales campaign
- Retail Marketing: Liaising with vendors and related teams to deploy in-store marketing assets, monitor visibility implementation, and ensure smooth execution on time in full
- Event Marketing: Organizing & coordinating events, workshops, and meetups for members & other professionals, C-level executives, to enhance brand visibility and foster community engagement
- Performance Tracking: Tracking and reporting weekly & monthly FnB revenue and performance leads to Manager

#### Accomplishment

Successfully expanded the Co-working Space & FnB chain by opening 3 additional locations & reopening 1 location within 6 months, ensuring consistent branding & performance across 5 locations



### **PHARMACITY PHARMACY JSC**

#### **Brand Marketing Intern**

- Campaign Development: Assisted in conducting competitor analysis, brainstorming ideas & executing in-store marketing activities & internal events, ensuring alignment with thematic concepts
- Media & Creative Coordination: Involved in creating branding content for variety of channels (POSM, Web Blog, Social Post) to enhance the visibilities & efficiency of brand team's campaigns
- Campaign Operations: Supported the smooth operation of in-store activations and execution of OOH, CSR campaigns
- Stakeholder Management: Liaised with agencies & cross-functional teams (Trading, Retail, Creative, Digital) to deploy monthly POSM & Marketing materials across diverse O2O touchpoints
- Customer Insight: Assisted CI team in creating questionnaires for surveys, collecting data, and reporting for Pharmacity's product updates & customer experience enhancements
- Co-Marketing Development: Supported BM in monitoring monthly partnership campaigns both online (Social, Gamification Package) & offline (OOH, in-store POSM)

#### Accomplishment

- · Experienced in executing monthly promotional marketing campaigns for master brand & PMC's private brand
- Successfully organized 6-month in-store activation in collaboration with Merck & Hoan My Hospital
- Executed CSR campaign partners with 175 Hospital in Tay Ninh Province

## EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES



## **MARTIC - IU MARKETING CLUB**

Oct 2019 - Aug 2021

### Head Of Creative and Media Department

- Brainstormed concept ideas, created campaign communication & social plans, developed art & content directions
- Designed visuals and wrote content for diverse marketing distributions (Social Media, Printed Materials, Email Digital, etc.)
- Managed consistent visual, content and traffic on social media channels with total about 8000 followers
- Effectively organized & led social 4 online & offline campaigns with 50-900 participations nationwide

#### Accomplishment

- Organized V Twist Competition 2019 a marketing arena with over 120 participants in HCM City.
- » Earned up to 55000 reaches for the opening poster and 1700 followers for the new fanpage.
- Conceptualized and executed Series Webinar: Marketing Exploration 2021 a series of 3 online workshops about Marketing.
- » Attracted over 900 participation registrations and gained 400 new followers for the fanpage within 1-month of event.

#### **EDUCATION**



### **INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY - VNU HCMC**

2019 - 2023

#### Bachelor of Business Administration - Marketing Major

- GPA: 3.35/4.00 (Classification: Very Good)
- Relative courses: Marketing Strategy (87), Brand Management (85)

### **SKILLS**

## **Technical Skills**

Data Analysis: SPSS, SQL

Microsoft Office: Word (MOS 2016), Excel, PowerPoint Designing: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Canva



#### CERTIFICATION

**IFITS** 2023

Band: 6.5

#### **Kev Strenaths**

Creativity, Project Management, Communication Skill, Leadership











